[Isn't it thrilling?]
[I think so.]
[Do you know?]
[An avalanche]
[starts with a single snowflake.]
You're here.
I'm waiting for you.
Sister Qianqian, you look gorgeous today.
You look like a bride.
You're so sweet.
Take a break.
I'll call you later.
Yes, Miss Lu.
Hey,
what's going on with you?
It's my wedding day,
and you look even more stressed than I do.
Something happened at the company?
Just a few things
that need to be dealt with.
It's okay.
Don't frown.
If something bad happens,
I'll take care of it.
I'm gonna wear the wedding dress you designed
to be the most beautiful bride.
The bride is the most important person today.
I'll do whatever you want.
Hello.
Okay, I'm coming.
I have to go out for something urgent.
Miss Lu Qianqian.
Qianqian,
are you okay?
Are you
feeling unwell?
I'm fine.
I just stayed up too late last night,
so I'm a bit groggy.
Miss Lu Qianqian,
do you take Mr. Zhou Jian to be your lawful wedded husband?
For better or for worse,
in sickness and in health,
to love, honor and cherish him,
and to be his loving haven
until death do you part?
I
do.
Now,
let's welcome our lovely angel
to present the rings
[to the newlyweds.]
You're late to your sister's wedding.
Is it because you haven't been home?
and have been hanging out outside?
Are you spying on me?
You're the most eye-catching wherever you go.
Do I need to spy on you?
[This small ring]
[has no beginning and no end,]
[symbolizing your eternal and complete commitment to each other.]
Now,
please exchange rings
and lock in your promise of happiness.
What did you do to my sister?
She looks very abnormal.
At this moment,
the ring finger is no longer nameless.
She just saw clearly
what was crawling under that gorgeous satin.
Please join hands
and raise your glasses together
with all your loved ones
and share this sweetness and happiness.
Sister.
Brother-in-law.
How are you?
It's such a big day today.
Are you happy?
You...
Qianqian.
The guests are still here.
Are you done?
Miss Lu,
your mouth is bleeding. Wipe it.
I'll wait for you at the wedding dress store.
You just finished the ceremony.
Why are you hiding here alone?
Where's your husband?
You finally saw it.
I was thinking
of finding a suitable time
to tell you.
1%.
Sign it,
and the 1% of shares will be yours.
The condition is,
before I come back from abroad,
I don't care how you do it,
just get rid of all the women
related to Zhou Jian.
I don't want
any trouble afterwards.
Yan,
take out the autumn clothes from my cloakroom,
iron them, and tidy them up.
Then find two pairs of shoes
and put them in the suitcase.
Yes, ma'am.
You're leaving early tomorrow morning?
Is it that urgent?
Yeah.
The plane tickets are booked.
Why do you suddenly go to Singapore?
I never
heard you mention it before.
I'm gonna meet an old friend.
I'm afraid you're too busy to go with me,
so I'll go for two days by myself.
I'll be back soon.
Qianqian,
what happened to you today?
I'm full.
Why did you hit Lu Xu?
I'm going to rest.
Miss Lu,
that's the Ms. Li you're looking for.
Thank you.
Hello, Dean Li.
I'm Lu Qianqian,
coming from abroad.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I know who you are.
You know me?
You are the child of Lu Jingcheng and Yu Wen.
You must have remembered wrong.
Lu Jingcheng is my father,
but my mother
is called Annie.